Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Records WAG.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: General Files
  - Subseries B: 1945-2004.
    - Correspondence: Duncan, Angus/Executive Secretary (found in 1958 file of Committee on the Integration of the Negro in the Theatre), 1959 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Jones, Paul G./Assistant Executive Secretary, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Form Letters: Information Pertaining to Letter Form Contract and to Stock Company Members re: Health Insurance, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Legislation, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Television: "closed" Circuit, Subscription, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 26A)
    - Theatre Authority: Minutes, Jan 20, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - United Service Organizations (USO), 1959 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Welfare and Pension Benefits: Report for the Members of Actors Equity, Feb 16, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - West Coast: Hollywood Area Theatres (HAT) Contract, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Actors' Fund, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Actors' Studio, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Agency: Committee, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Agency: Correspondence, General, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Commissions, Jan 1960-Jun 1960 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Commissions, Jul 1960-Dec 1960 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Contracts with Members, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - Aliens: General, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - American Federation of Labor, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (ANTA), 1960 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (ANTA): Minutes, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - American Theatre Wing, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - American Theatre Wing: Tony Awards and Stork Club Luncheon Controversy, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Annual Meeting, Mar 25, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Association of Civic Musical Theatres, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Atkinson, Brooks Tribute, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Bonding, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Broadway Blackout: Broadway Company Correspondence including Copies of Notices from Management, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Broadway Blackout: Correspondence During Lockout/Strike, Jun 1, 2005-Jun 9, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Broadway Blackout: Correspondence re: Pension and Welfare Plans, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Broadway Blackout: Correspondence re: Pension and Welfare Plans, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 11A)
    - Broadway Blackout: Correspondence, Settlement and Beyond, Jun 10, 2005-Dec 1, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Broadway Blackout: Correspondence to May 31, 1960, pre Lockout/Strike (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Broadway Blackout: Equity-League Negotiations (Agendas, Minutes), 1960 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Broadway Blackout: Negotiating Committee Contract Proposals, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Broadway Blackout: Negotiating Committee Correspondence, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Broadway Blackout: New Rules Negotiated, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Broadway Blackout: Press Clippings, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Broadway Show League, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Broadway Show League: "Talent '60", 1960 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Chicago: Café Theatre Contract, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Chicago Office, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Colleges and Universities, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Committee: Advisory Committee on Chorus Affairs (ACCA), 1960 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Committee: American Guild of Musical Artists (AGMA) Merger, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Committee: Baby Bundles Bureau, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Committee: Election Procedures, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Committee: Ethnic Minorities, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Committee: House Affairs, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Committee: Industrial Shows, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Committee: Legislative, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Committee: Membership Relations, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Committee: Night Club Contract, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Committee: Pay-TV, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Committee: Stock and Off-Broadway, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Committee: Stock, Dramatic, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Committee: Stock, Musical, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Committee: To Extend the Professional Theatre, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Committee: Trade Union Theatre, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Committees: General, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Appearing non-Equity, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Bellamy, Ralph, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Bikel, Theodore, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Children's Theatre, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Duncan, Angus/Executive Secretary, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: General, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Gibberson, William/Department of Theatre Promotion and then Assistant Executive Secretary, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Irving, Ben/ Assistant Executive Secretary, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Members Appearing in Church Sponsored Activities, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Moore, Dick/Editor Equity Magazine, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: re: the Death of Paul G. Jones, Assistant Executive Secretary, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Shubert, John and the Exempt List, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Theatres-New Prospects, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - Council, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 30)
    - Cuts Board, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 31)
    - Defaulting Managers List, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 32)
    - Derwent Awards, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 33)
    - Equity Library Theatre, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 34)
    - Equity Library Theatre: "Dead End" Production and Sit-In, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 35)
    - Equity Library Theatre West, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 36)
    - Income Tax, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 37)
    - Jurisdictional Dispute: "Dairyman's Association Show", 1960 (Box 39, Folder 38)
    - Jurisdictional Dispute: "Laughs and Other Events", 1960 (Box 39, Folder 39)
    - Jurisdictional Dispute: "The Riddle of Sheba", 1960 (Box 39, Folder 40)
    - Labor Day Parade, Sep 5, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 41)
    - Lambs Laboratory Theatre, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 42)
    - Legislation, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 43)
    - Legislation: Gilbert Bill re: Relation to Employment Agencies, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 44)
    - Membership Correspondence, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 45)
    - Membership Correspondence: Insurance, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 46)
    - Membership Meetings, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 47)
    - Moral Re-Armament: Invitation to "Hoffnung", 1960 (Box 39, Folder 48)
    - National Council on the Arts and Government, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 49)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 50)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Nominating Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Off-Broadway, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Off-Broadway: Coffee House Theatres, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Readings, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Records of the Committee of Experts on the International Protection of Performers, Producers of Phonograms and Broadcasters (The Hague), May 9, 2005-May 20, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Rules and Regulations: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Safe and Sanitary Conditions, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Show Business, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Stock: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Stock: Council of Resident Theatres (CORST), 1960 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Stock: Council of Resident Theatres (CORST) Contract, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Stock: Council of Stock Theatres (COST), 1960 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Stock: Council of Stock Theatres (COST) Contract, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Stock: Musical Arena Theatre Association (MATA), 1960 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Stock: Musical Arena Theatre Association (MATA) Contract, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Stock: Musical Contract, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Stock: Outdoor Drama, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Stock: Outdoor Drama Contract, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Stock: Security Agreement Rider, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Television: Subscription TV, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Traveling Representatives, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Theatre Authority: Correspondence, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Theatre Authority: Minutes, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Theatre Authority: Statements of Cash Condition, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Theatre Industry Advisory Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Toronto Advisory Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Toronto: Equity Showcase Theatre, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Toronto: Membership Meeting Minutes, Feb 21, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Toronto Office, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Toronto: O'Keefe Centre for the Performing Arts, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - United Service Organizations (USO), 1960 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Membership Meetings, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - West Coast: San Francisco Office, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - West Coast: West Coast Advisory Committee, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Actors Fund, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Admissions Tax, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Agency: Committee, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Commission, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Commission Dispute-Al Lewis and William Gibberson of AEA, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Commission Dispute-Patricia Wilson and Ray Smith of the Ashley Steiner Agency, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Commission Dispute-Robert Holiday and Nick Argenta and TARA (Theatrical Artists Representatives Association), 1961 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Agency: General, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Agency: Theatrical Artists Representatives Association (TARA), 1961 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Aliens: Committee, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Aliens: Correspondence, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Aliens: Rules, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (ANTA), 1961 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (ANTA): Minutes, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - American Theatre Wing, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Annual Meeting, Mar 24, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Associacion Puertorriquena de Artistas y Technicos del Espectaculo (APATE) (Puerto Rico Association of Artists and Technicians re: Hotel Dispute, Jan 1961-Apr 1961 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Associacion Puertorriquena de Artistas y Technicos del Espectaculo (APATE) (Puerto Rico Association of Artists and Technicians re: Hotel Dispute, May 1961-Sep 1961 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Bonding, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Broadway Show League, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Broadway Show League: "Talent '61", 1961 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Chicago: Happy Medium Contract, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Chicago Office, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Coffee Houses: "Report(s) of Employment of Equity Members in Coffee Shops", 1961 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Colleges and Universities, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Committee: Advisory Committee on Chorus Affairs (ACCA), 1961 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Committee: Advisory Committee on Chorus Affairs (ACCA) Minutes, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Committee: Baby Bundles Bureau, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Committee: Election Procedures, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - Committee: Equity-AGMA (American Guild of Musical Artists) Merger, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Committee: Equity-League, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Committee: Ethnic Minorities, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Committee: Fact Finding, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Committee: Industrial Shows, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Committee: Legislation, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Committee: Pay-As-You-See Television, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Committee: Repertory Theatre, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 35A)
    - Committee: Special Council Committee to Hear Charges Brought by Felix Munso Against Iggie Wolfington, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - Committee: Special Grievance Committee re: Felix Munso Statement at Membership Meeting, Jan 1961 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - Committee: Special Grievance Committee re: Felix Munso Statement at Membership Meeting, Jul 1961-Oct 1961 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - Committee: Stock and Off-Broadway, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Committees: General, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Community Theatre, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Appearing non-Equity, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Appearing non-Equity at Arundel Opera Theatre in 1960, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Charges Against Dick Lamb, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Charges Against William "Bill" McHale, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Charges and Fine for Rick Davis, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Congress Hotel, Baltimore, Maryland, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Duncan, Angus/Executive Secretary, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Dullzell, Paul Death, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: General, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Gibberson, William/Assistant Executive Secretary, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Insurance Department, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Integration/Segregation in Theatre(s), 1961 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Issues re: Television and Televising, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Legal Department, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Letter Form Contract, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: non-Equity Theatres, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Members Appearing in Church Sponsored Activities, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: re: Trial of Michael St. John, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Schnitzer, Robert C./Executive Director of University of Michigan Theatre, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: United States Information Agency, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Council, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Council: Election Recount, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Cuts Board, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Defaulting Managers List, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Entertainment Workers Founding Congress/San Jose, Costa Rica, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Equity-AGMA (American Guild of Musical Artists) Discussions, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Equity Library Theatre, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Equity Library Theatre West, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Industrial Shows Agreement, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Labor Day Parade, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Lambs Club: Productions, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Legislation, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Legislation: HR 4172 and 4174, to Establish a Federal Advisory Council on the Arts and Grants to States, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Membership Correspondence, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Membership Correspondence: Insurance, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Membership Meetings, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - National Council on the Arts and Government, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - New Dramatists Committee, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - New York City Central Labor Council, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - New York State AFL-CIO: Includes Anti-Segregation Resolution, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Nominating Committee: Including Independent Ticket Petitions, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Off Broadway: Correspondence, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Off Broadway: Negotiating Committee, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - "Plays for Living" a Project of Family Service Association of America, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Readings, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Recording: for the Blind, for Theatre Archives, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Safe and Sanitary Reports, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Signet Players: non-Equity Company wanting Guest Artists, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Stock: Correspondence, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Stock: Council of Stock Theatres, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Stock: Musical Arena Theatre Association, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Stock: Outdoor Drama, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Theatre Authority, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Theatre Authority Minutes, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Theatre Communications Group (TCG), 1961 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Toronto: Annual Membership Meeting, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Toronto: Canadian Advisory Committees (Toronto, Montreal), 1961 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Toronto Office, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Unemployment Insurance, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - United Service Organizations (USO), 1961 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Membership Meeting, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - West Coast: Los Angeles Office, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - West Coast: San Francisco Office, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - West Coast: West Coast Advisory Committee, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - World's Fair (1964-1965): Correspondence and Other Materials, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Actors' Equity Foundation, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Actors' Fund, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Admissions Tax, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Agency: Committee, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Agency: Correspondence re: Commission, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Agency: Correspondence re; Contracts with Members, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Agency: Franchises Cancelled, Revoked, Suspended, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Agency: General, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Aliens: Committee, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Aliens: Correspondence, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Aliens: Rules, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - American National Theatre and Academy (ANTA), 1962 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - American Theatre Wing, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, Mar 23, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Anti-Discrimination: Casting and Employment of the Negro Performer, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Anti-Discrimination Clause: Correspondence, General, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Anti-Discrimination Clause: Correspondence re: Huntsville, Alabama and other Southern Venues, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Anti-Discrimination: Congressman Adam Clayton Powell's Committee Hearings on Discrimination Against Negro and Puerto Rican Performers, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Backers' Auditions, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Bonding, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - British-American Exchange: "Beyond the Fringe" (UK), "The Premise" (US), 1962 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Broadway Show League, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Chicago: Happy Medium Contract, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Chicago Office, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Colleges and Universities: Including Use of the Anti-Discrimination Clause, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Committee: Advisory Committee on Chorus Affairs (ACCA), 1962 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Committee: Baby Bundles Bureau, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Committee: Canadian Affairs, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Committee: Election Procedures, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Committee: Ethnic Minorities, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Committee: Industrial Shows, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Committee: Legislation, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Committee: Night Club and Café Theatres, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Committee: Pay-As-You-See Television, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Committee: Repertory Theatre, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 29A)
    - Committee: Stage Managers, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Committee: Stock and Off-Broadway, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Committee: Stock Negotiations, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Committee: To Extend the Professional Theatre, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Committee: Trade Union Theatre, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Committees: General, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Community Theatre, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Contract Changes and Concessions, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Contracts, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence: Appearing non-Equity, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence: Bellamy, Ralph, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence: Davis, Dorothy/ Attorney, West Coast, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence: Dullzell, Paul Estate, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence: Duncan, Angus/Executive Secretary, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence: General, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence: Gibberson, William/ Assistant Executive Secretary, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence: Holbrook, Hal ("Mark Twain Tonight") Playing in the South, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence: Insurance Department, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence: Irving, Ben/Assistant Executive Secretary, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence: Legal Department, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence: Munso, Felix, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence: Shubert, John, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence: United States Information Agency, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence: Variety International Productions, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Zulkie, Lambert/Assistant Administrative Secretary, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Council, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Cuts Board: Stars Only, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Defaulting Managers List, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Election: Charges Against Douglas Gregory by Theodore Bikel, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Election: "Sample Ballot" Controversy, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Equity-AGMA (American Guild of Musical Artists) Merger Discussions, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Equity Library Theatre, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Equity Library Theatre West, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Industrial Shows, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Institute for Advanced Studies in the Theatre Arts, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Inter-American Federation of Entertainment Workers 2nd Congress, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Lambs Club: Productions, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Legislation, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Legislation: Arts, Arts Education, Federal Advisory Council on the Arts, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Legislation: Entertainment Expense Tax Deductions, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Legislation: Golodner, Jack /Equity Legislative Representative, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Membership Meetings, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - National Council on the Arts and Government, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Nominating Committee, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Nomination Petitions, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Off-Broadway, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Pension and Welfare Fund, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Proposed Campaign: Actors as Poor Credit Risks, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 27)